boxbilling.com 2017-12-02

# Billing and client management software

### Effective

This Policy was last modified on April 26, 2017.

### Information Practices

Boxbilling, LLC Company Code 302788919 ("Company") understands that security and privacy are important issues for visitors to our web site, boxbilling.com (the "Site") and recognises our obligation to keep your information secure and confidential. That is why we maintain the following standards to help protect information that personally identifies you. We may modify this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") at any time and, accordingly, we urge you to frequently review the Policy. We will always apply the Policy under which your information was collected, unless we obtain your prior consent.

### Collection of Information

You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, surname, address, email address, country of residence ("Personal Information") that will be used in connection with the BoxBilling software and/or that is required to have access to some features of the Site. By using the Site and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Policy. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, and this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain services. We or our business partners may also collect information that is anonymous, such as your IP number (a number used to identify your computer on the Internet) or the type of browser you are using ("Anonymous Information"), through the use of cookies or by other means. We hope that, by using Anonymous Information, we can update the Site to make it more useful to you and other users. We reserve the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information, without limitation.

### Use of Information

We use your Personal Information for the following purposes: for use in connection with the BoxBilling software; to provide the services and customer support you request; to process your transactions and send notices about your transaction; to administer your account; to resolve disputes, collect fees and for troubleshooting; to administer and improve the Site and related services; to notify you of our products, services, promotional events or special offers that maybe of interest to you; to provide Internet security; and to meet legal requirements. We may work with our business partners who may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as sending email messages, managing data or hosting the Site. These business partners have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally required to do so. We may use third party advertising companies to place ads on the Site and to place our ads on other web sites. These companies may use Anonymous Information about your visits to this and other web sites to provide advertisements on the Site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If the Company is involved in the sale of a substantial portion of its business assets, Anonymous or Personal Information maybe among the transferred assets.

### Retention and Modification of Information

Collected Personal Information is stored for 6 months from the moment last service is provided, unless until this moment you request that we remove the data by contacting us at [[email protected]](http://www.boxbilling.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) If you wish to update or to correct your Personal Information provided to us, please contact us via [[email protected]](http://www.boxbilling.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or enter your members area to update or to correct your Personal Information.

### Invitations By Registered Users

You can invite friends to become registered users by sending an invitation email via our automated invitation system. We store the email addresses that you provide so that we may keep track of how many people are being invited. We do not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication. Recipients of invitations may contact us at [[email protected]](http://www.boxbilling.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request the removal of their information from our database.

### E-mail Communications

When you send an email to us, you are communicating with Company electronically. You thereby consent to receive communications from Company electronically. Company will communicate with you by email or by posting notices on the Site. All agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that Company provides to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

### Cookies

When you visit the Site, we may passively collect certain information without your prior consent. Such information (collected in standard web server logs) may include your IP address, browser type, and web access times. Such passively collected information is used in standard web traffic analysis, in conjunction with demographic/aggregate analysis of collected user records.

We may also collect information through the use of "cookies" which are small computer files that are transferred to a computer's hard drive and which permit us to know about site visits. We may use cookies or similar technology to improve your experience on the Site by making it easier for you to navigate through the Site or to make a Site feature work better. Information collected from a "cookie" might include information regarding your browser, type of computer, operating system, Internet service provider and other similar information. Cookie technology may also gather information about the areas you visit on our Site and about the links you may select from within our Site to other areas of the Internet.

We do not extract Personal Information during this process. Currently, we use both session and persistent cookies. Session cookies are used to maintain tracking of a user through an application and expire at the end of a web page visit. Persistent cookies do not expire at the end of the session. Persistent cookies are stored on your hard drive and read by your browser each time you visit the Site. Such cookies contain only a numeric session identifier. We use such information in the aggregate to understand which services and resources our visitors prefer and how those services and resources are used. We may share aggregate demographic/statistical information with third parties.

With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site's features.

### Links

The Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the collection or use of your Personal or Anonymous Information at any third party sites. Therefore, the Company disclaims any liability for any third party's use of your Personal or Anonymous Information obtained through using a third party web site.

### Security

We have policies and procedures in place to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information that we collect and maintain. All Personal Information is stored on secured servers, behind a firewall at a data center with access to data strictly controlled. We use Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your user passwords and personal credit information, including your credit card number and expiration date, before it travels over the Internet. Any unauthorised use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution.

### Privacy Rights

Personal Information can be seen, updated and corrected in members area. If you want to receive a disclosure of Personal Information and get more details about Personal Information handling make a request by email at: [[email protected]](http://www.boxbilling.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) This can be done once a year for free.

### Contacting the Company

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us by email at [[email protected]](http://www.boxbilling.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) Please provide a concise communication with complete information, including your contact information.

BOXBILLING, LLC  
Address: Vijokliu g. 23, LT-50143, Kaunas, Lithuania  
Company Code: 302788919  
Email: [[email protected]](http://www.boxbilling.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* * *

## Use of cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide web services and functionalities for the users. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies. A persistent cookie consists of a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, which will be stored by the browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date). A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

## Site cookies

The table below explains the site cookies we use at boxbilling.com and why we use them.

Cookie Source | Cookie Name | Function | Expiry Date  
---|---|---|---  
boxbilling | is_returning | This cookie is used for login and comment functions on this site. It is created in order to track whether a visitor is new or returning. A "returning" visitor is one that has previously visited any tracked page on your domain within the last 5 years. | 5 years from the date that it was set  
boxbilling | _rfrr | This cookie is a persistent cookie used for storing internal reports regarding Google Analytics information | 1,000 days from the date that it was set  
boxbilling | _rfrr_start_time | This cookie is a persistent cookie used for tracking sign up time of the visitor | 1,000 days from the date that it was set  
boxbilling | _trk | This cookie is a persistent cookie in order to track whether a visitor is new or returning. A "returning" visitor is one that has previously visited any tracked page on your domain within the last 90 days. It also tracks personal information about you in order to prefill forms on website. | 90 days from the date that it was set  
boxbilling | PHPSESSID | This cookie is a session cookie used to establish a user session and to pass state data via a temporary cookie | session and to pass state data via a temporary cookie end of session/close of browser  
  
## Third party cookies

The table below explains the third party cookies we use and why we use them. These cookies are set by a third party and not by this site.

Cookie Source | Cookie Name | Function | Expiry Date  
---|---|---|---  
Google Analytics | _utma _utmb _utmc _utmz | These cookies belong to third parties and are used to collect information on how visitors use this site. Collected information is used to compile reports and to help improving the site. The cookies collect information in an anonym way, including (i) the number of visitors to the site, (ii) where visitors have come to this site from and (iii) the pages of this site they visited. Click here for an overview of privacy at Google. | _utma: 2 years from the date that it was set _utmb: 30 mins from the date that it was set _utmc: end of session/close of browser _utmz: 6 months from the date that it was set  
Google AdSense | _ar_v4 | These cookies are set by our advertising partner Google in order to show you relevant adverts. | 6 years from the date that it was set  
  
## Don't Accept Cookies

If you do not want to accept cookies you should end your browsing on this site. Please note that the above button do not block third party cookies. Third party cookies can be deleted by changing cookie setting in your browser as further described below.

## Change cookie settings in your browser

Most web browsers allow control of the above listed cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see, what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Please note that if cookie settings in your browser are changed the above functions specified under section 3 may not be available.

## Cookies and personal information

Cookies do not contain any information that personally identifies you, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained only from Avangate Tracking cookies.

## Privacy policy and cookies policy

This Cookies policy constitutes an inseparable part of the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy of this site.
